Don't freak out
It's not like a real "date"
Then what?
I mean
let's play a couple
Homosexual marriage
is legal now
You know, gay couple
is quite a trend
"The first gay couple
in showbiz"
Sounds cool, huh?
Honestly, I was told
to do this by my agency
Something came up
with their idol group
and I can't leave them
due to my contract
So what…
They wanna use us
to distract the public?
Don't you wanna be
Lee Hyesung
rather than
Yoon Minhyung now?
By the way
what makes you
so confident?
Did you expect me
to be touched
by your merciful offer?
What if I don't want to?
I don't like to be
involved in such a scam
I'd rather live as an
unknown actor for life
Am I not your type?
No
I like you, though
Since when did we…
But there's no option
It's already
been decided
Then why did you call me?
I just wanted to see
how you'd react
Seriously?
Only for that?
Yes
What's wrong with that?
The rumor was right
You asshole
Watch your language
to your boyfriend